Hello friends, welcome to Share
Market Expert. Those who are
visiting the channel for the first time, please
subscribe to the channel, share it and
press the bell icon so that you keep
getting notifications of upcoming videos. So in today's
video, we are going to discuss
ICI Lombard General Insurance Company,
whose results were declared today, so let's
see
what outcome of its meeting is coming out. So
first of all, if we talk about it,
today the company has been seen declaring an interim dividend of
Rs. 10 for each face value of Rs. 10, which will be
finalized in the next upcoming meeting.
Here, now we have come to the
annual result of ICI Lombard. Here,
if we talk about its total income, then
first of all you will see
its total
income in lakhs and in this, in this quarter you were
seen generating a revenue of Rs. 51613, whereas
in the last quarter you got Rs. 5315, so
here on quarter on quarter basis  But
you will see the revenue increasing,
where at 3 you saw the normal
revenue increasing for
ICI Lombard and if we look at it on a year-on-year basis, then on a
year-on-year basis you saw the
revenue also increasing,
almost at 9 you are seeing a jump in revenue on a year-on-year basis
and if we look at it in another way, then
you got to see a negative year-on-year basis, so
at 9 you are seeing a normal
revenue and you are seeing a positive
and if we talk about its profit, then
here at number 27 you are given the profit
after tax, so if we
talk about the profit of ICI Lombard General Insurance Limited Company, then
you are getting a profit of ₹1,1950
which is of the first last
quarter and if seen in its second last quarter, then
you will
see a profit of ₹4314,
so you are seeing a jump in profit here,
which on a quarter-on-quarter
basis you will get 20  But it has been seen increasing
and if we look at it on a year-
on-year basis, what are you seeing on a
year-on-year basis, then on a
year-on-year basis also you have
seen profit increasing here, on a
year-on-year basis also you are
seeing annual growth of about four percent, if we
talk about the shareholding pattern within the profit, then
in this quarter you will see the shareholding of the company
decreasing, decreasing,
in the last quarter you were at 52,
which has come down to 50.48.3
and if we look at the last annual, then
you are seeing a decrease here also, so the
promoters were seen reducing their holding a little bit
and if we look at the outcome of the result, then the
overall result you have
seen here is only consolidation numbers, consolidation, so what do
you have to do here tomorrow, there may be a
correction in ICI Lombard in the coming time,
you may see ICI Lombard below 10
in the coming time.
At 10, this
is our consolidation number and we can sell it here and
move ahead. In the coming time, you
may see a significant decline in the company. If
you liked the analysis of our results, then
please subscribe to the video,
share it and press the bell icon
so that you keep getting notifications of upcoming videos.
Thanks for watching.